Do you want to spend six
weeks in a sling
or would you rather start
moving tomorrow?
And we sort of said, let's
push the envelope
because my mom has had two
reverses.
You know, just because
you're 76,
not driving for six weeks
can really disable you
from your life, your
lifestyle, your family.
She drives my kids to
school.
And so really, we said, what
if we get people
moving earlier, our
techniques have gotten
we can push the envelope and
get people back faster.
And so we did a head-to-head
study.
We actually did one of my
partners
who did six weeks of
slinging,
and I did people in a week.
For a few days afterwards,
you start moving it right
away.
And we found that the
outcomes were similar,
no complications, no loss to
a patient.
And in fact, at six weeks,
they're doing a ton better.
So sometimes, evidence shows
it,
and you have to change what
you do.